Mike Dawicki

Senior CIS Major with hands-on experience with web development and deployment, developing and maintaining both SQL and NoSQL databases and cloud computing via AWS. Check out my portfolio by going to mikedawicki09.github!

mikedawicki99@gmail.com (267) 566-7674 Ivyland, PA



linkedin.com/in/michael-dawicki



Education

James Madison University, Harrisonburg, VA

Major GPA: 3.56

Bachelor of Business Administration (B.B.A.) in Computer Information Systems (Anticipated Graduation May 2021)

Technical Skills

Languages - C#, Java, Python, SQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScriptTools - Microsoft SQL server, Microsoft Visual Studio, Power BI, NetBeans, Oracle, AWSFrameworks - Bootstrap, ASP.NET

Project Experience

CIS Senior Capstone Project, James Madison University

Jan. 2021-Apr. 2021

- Developed an information system using an object-oriented approach for a client in the Harrisonburg community using C# and ASP.NET which was picked among
- Major contributor to the system that was picked among the top two teams to present to a judge panel, CIS students, and CIS professors
- Responsible for both hosting our system on Amazon's Elastic Beanstalk as well as uploading our database onto Amazon's Relational Database Services
- To increase performance and make our system more robust, I dockerized our application via AWS Fargate

Amazon Web Services DynamoDB Project

Mar. 2021- Apr. 2021

- Created, manipulated and queried an AWS DynamoDB Database by using Python IDLE
- Gained relevant experience using AWS services including IAM and Amazon's non-relational database DynamoDB

Portfolio Website Jan. 2021

- Developed a fully responsive portfolio website using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Bootstrap
- Deployed and implemented website via GitHub pages

Employment Experience

DSG Electrical Contractor, Electrical Apprentice, Morrisville, PA

Jan. 2016-Present

- Assisted mechanics in the field by helping install, repair and maintain electrical systems
- Maintained the cleanliness of the warehouse by organizing supplies and materials

La Stalla Italian Restaurant, Busser, Ivyland PA

May 2018-May 2019

- Engaged with wait staff to handle all customer necessities
- Worked in a team-oriented environment to maintain cleanliness

Certifications

- Amazon Web Services Cloud Practitioner Essentials
- LinkedIn Learning: Introduction to Programming Using Python